questions = [
    {
        "id":1,
        "question":"There are 1,200 elephants in a herd. Some have pink and blue stripes, some are all pink and some are all blue. Of these one third are pure pink. \
        Is true that 400 elephants are definitely blue",
        "answer":"No",
        "options":[
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"WWhich vowel comes midway between J and T",
        "answer":"O",
        "options":[
            "O",
            "T",
            "U"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"Which number comes next in this series of number? 1 2 3 5 7 11 13 ?",
        "answer":"17",
        "options":[
            "15",
            "17",
            "14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"Which letter comes next in this series of letters ? B A C B D C E D F",
        "answer":"E",
        "options":[
            "E",
            "A",
            "F"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"1, 7, 2, 7, 3, (), ()",
        "answer":"7,4",
        "options":[
            "4,7",
            "7,4",
            "4,8"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"128, 64, 32, 16, 8, (), ()",
        "answer":"4,2",
        "options":[
            "0,8",
            "1,0",
            "4,2"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"4, 5, 7, 8, 10, (), ()",
        "answer":"11,12",
        "options":[
            "13,14",
            "11,13",
            "11,12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question":"2, 3, 30, 31, 310, (), ()",
        "answer":"311,3110",
        "options":[
            "312,313",
            "311,312",
            "311,3110"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question":"2, 4, 6, 5, 7, (), ()",
        "answer":"9,8",
        "options":[
            "9,8",
            "9,11",
            "9,9"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"7, 4, 9, 16, 11, (), ()",
        "answer":"64,13",
        "options":[
            "64,13",
            "16,21",
            "19,23"
        ]
    }
    
]

# count = 0
# age = input("What is your age? ")
# for i in questions:
#     print(i["question"])
#     for j in i["options"]:
#         print(j)
#     res = input("What is your own answer: ? ")
#     if res.lower() == i["answer"].lower():
#          count+=1
# print("Weldone press enter yes / y to see your score")
# print()
# if (input() == "Yes" or input() == "y"):
#     print("Your score is {}".format(count))
    
# iq = (age * 100)/count
# print("Your IQ is {}".format(iq))